# ABOUTME

I offer 3 and a half years of experience in software development.

Currently I am working as a Software Engineer for Sainsbury's in Coventry UK.

My goal is to keep learning and growing my career as a Full-Stack Software Engineer with Cloud technologies.

Programming is my passion. I also like working with cloud and infrastructure technologies.

# CONTACT



atanasskambitov@gmail.com



+44 744 87 19 858



https://github.com/NASOKILA



https://www.linkedin.com/in/atanaskambitov-a69528162/

# EDUCATION



SOUTH-WEST UNIVERSITY "NEOFIT RILSKI" Bachelor's degree in informatics 15/09/2014 - 25/05/2018 (4 years)



SOFTUNI "PRIVATE SOFTWARE UNIVERSITY" Graduated C# and JavaScript engineer 05/12/2016 - 21/02/2018 (2 years)



https://github.com/NASOKILA/Diplomas-Certificates

# ATANAS KAMBITOV SOFTWARE ENGINEER

## **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

Sainsbury's – United Kingdom, Coventry

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

03/12/2018 - NOW (1.5 YEARS)

Currently working on multiple projects mostly with C#, .Net, Azure, ReactJS, SQL and more. Managing infrastructure using Terraform, CI/CD pipelines IAAS, PAAS, SAAS, BAAS, FAAS and container orchestration with Kubernetes cluster.

Experience in Azure, AWS and GCP mostly in Serverless architecture, Microservices, Cloud Native Apps, Full-stack development including Unit and Integration testing.

Hands on experience in C#, .Net Core, ReactJS, React Hooks, Redux, SQL, TSQL, EF Core, Dapper, MongoDB, Azure, AWS, GCP, S3, SNS, Lambda, VISION API, AUTOML, DevOps, AKS, EKS, GCE, Docker, Signal R, Key vaults, AAD, Redis Cache, Container Registry, App Services, Azure Cosmos Db, Service Bus, Event Hubs, App Services REST, SOAP, OOP and more.

Usage of Power BI for reporting and Datadog for monitoring and alerting. Working in an agile way using scrum in a team of five people providing quality, latency, stability and performance following solid principles and design patterns.

# SoftUni – Bulgaria, Sofia

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

#### 05/12/2016 - 21/12/2018 (2 YEARS)

Design and deliver backend RESTFULL API's using .Net Core and NodeJS + ExpressJS. Build and release frontend applications with ReactJS and Angular 2+. Experience with MVC, MVVM, REST, SOAP XML, JSON, YAML, Git, GitHub and more.

Optimizing SQL queries and working on relational databases with SQL, Dapper, and Entity framework.

Quickly deliver quality code and meet deadlines on multiple projects using different technologies, languages and frameworks.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Azure | AWS | GCP | Microservices | Serverless | AKS | EKS | GCE | Docker | Agile Methodologies | Scrum | IAAS | PAAS | BAAS | FAAS | C# | .Net Core | Node.js & Express.js | MVC & MVVM | RESTFUL API's | SQL | Mongo DB ReactJS | Angular | Redux | TypeScript | JavaScript | jQuery | Bootstrap | Solid Principles Design Patterns | HTML5 & CSS3 | Less & Sass | Git & GitHub

# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

.Net Core

https://github.com/NASOKILA/Tangy-Restaurant

.Net Core and ReactJS

https://github.com/NASOKILA/todolist.backend

Angular

https://nasokila.github.io/comix-shop https://github.com/NASOKILA/Portfolio-Projects/tree/comix-shop

## **LANGUAGES**

English | Italian | Spanish | Bulgarian